《致命女人》前情提要
Previously on Why Women Kill...
操
Fuck!
我知道这看起来很糟糕
I-I know that it looks bad.
明天一早你就去戒毒所
You're going to rehab first thing in the morning.
我不准你花钱了
You are cut off.
我觉得对我来说时机不合适
I-I-I don't think it's the best time for me right now.
你没有别的选择
You don't really have a choice here.
我的剧本刚卖了一百二十万
I just sold a script for $1.2 million.
我觉得我的选择多得很
You know, I think I got a lot of fucking choices.
我们走  洁德
Come on, Jade.
我想帮助他最好的方式
I think maybe the best way to help him
-就是留下来  -你们都去死吧
- is to stay here. - Fuck you both.
我有一个预约
Uh, I have an appointment.
这预约和你的新男朋友赫克托有关吗
And would this appointment involve your new boyfriend Hector?
他也许会一起来  没错
He may tag along, yes.
我毕业典礼后两天出发去巴黎
I, uh, leave for Paris two days after graduation.
想一起来吗
Care to join me?
-你应该去  -你不会有事吧
- You should go. - You'll be okay?
我会很开心的
I'll be delightful.
你会战胜这病的  爱你的  赫克托
你必须克服对有妇之夫的痴迷
You've got get over this obsession with another woman's husband.
我怀孕了
I'm pregnant.
你觉得他会有什么反应
How do you think he'll react?
-我觉得他会很激动的  -摊牌
- He will be thrilled. - Come clean.
告诉他外遇和孩子的事情你都知道
Tell him you know about the affair and the baby.
如果...他没有选我怎么办
What if... he doesn't choose me?
你难道还没受够这些谎言吗
Aren't you done with all the lies?
我们真的得谈谈
We definitely need to have a talk.
你吓到我了
You're starting to scare me.
我也害怕
I'm scared, too.
我一旦告诉你
Once I tell you,
一切都将不一样
everything is going to be different.
你病了吗
Are you sick?
我病了
I'm sick.
亲爱的  怎么了
Baby, what's wrong?
我得癌症了
I have cancer.
天啊  我的天
Oh, my... oh, my God.
致命女人
第一季  第八集
情人
我要死了
I'm going to die.
我不确定什么时候
I'm not sure when.
我只知道有一天我会离开
I just know one day I won't be here.
我害怕与上帝见面
I'm afraid to meet God.
我得为我的罪行负责
I'll have to account for my sins.
我罪孽深重
I have sinned a lot.
我和一个有妇之夫有染
I had an affair with a married man.
我睡了另一个男人的老婆
I slept with another guy's wife.
我和一对夫妻做爱
I had sex with a married couple
我差不多和我遇见过的所有人都发生过关系
and pretty much everyone else I ever met.
现在我未婚却有了身孕
Now I'm pregnant and unmarried.
我妈妈不知道我坠入爱河
My mom has no idea I've fallen in love.
泰勒不知道是我给了伊莱毒品
Taylor doesn't know I gave Eli drugs.
我不会告诉罗伯
I'm not going to tell Rob.
我要向萨蒙妮求婚
I'm gonna propose to Simone.
我八成会否定一切
I'll probably deny everything.
等我见到上帝时  我会乞求祂的宽恕
When I do meet God, I'll just beg his forgiveness.
我会感谢祂让我遇见了完美女人
I'll thank him for sending me the perfect woman.
我会说我做了我必须做的事
I'll say I did what I had to
只为求生
to survive.
希拉
Sheila.
我的天
Oh, my God.
我一直如坐针毡  你昨晚和罗伯谈了吗
I've been on pins and needles. Did you talk to Rob last night?
谈了
I did.
结果呢  我快急死了
So? I'm dying here.
你告诉他你知道他出轨后
How did he react when you told him
他作何反应
you knew that he was cheating on you?
这个
Well,
我们的对话发展方向出人意料
the conversation went in a surprising direction.
你说了什么  你说了什么
You said what? You said what?
什么  你怎么能那么说
What? How could you say that?
你怎么能那么说  贝丝·安
How could you say that, Beth Ann?
你在想什么  你在想什么
What are you thinking? What are you thinking?
我不敢相信你那么说了
I can't even believe you just said that!
赶紧回来  我好跟你说清楚
Get back here so I can give it to you!
都怪你妈妈
It's your mother's fault.
显然  她忘了教你一些基本原则
Clearly, she forgot to teach you some of the basics.
比如长大后  别假装患有癌症
Things like, when you grow up, don't pretend to have cancer.
女人每天都会骗她们的丈夫
Women lie to their husbands every day.
有的会在花了多少钱上面撒谎
Some lie about how much they spend.
而我的谎言是我要死了
My lie's that I'm dying.
就因为你一副高雅的样子
Just because you act classy
不代表你没疯掉
doesn't mean you're not fucking crazy.
我的疯癫不是没有目的的
There is a method to my madness.
罗伯绝不会在我生病时离开我
Rob will never leave me while I'm sick.
可万一艾普尔决定
But what if April decides
告诉他她怀上了他的孩子呢
to tell him that she's having his kid?
这个时候她的好朋友希拉就要登场了
That is where her good friend Sheila comes in.
我会劝她离开
I'm going to convince her to leave town.
开始新生活  彻底斩断和他的关系
Start a new life, sever the tie for good.
然后  等她出局后
And then, once she's out of the picture
罗伯就会属于我一个人
and I have Rob all to myself,
我的癌症也会奇迹般痊愈
my cancer will be miraculously cured.
我以前觉得你的微笑迷人
I used to find that little grin charming.
现在快吓死我了
Now it just scares the shit out of me.
女士们
Ladies.
你们可以进去看医生了
The doctor will see you now.
恩佐
Enzo.
希拉姑妈
Aunt Sheila.
瞧瞧穿白大褂的你
Look at you in the white coat.
这是我邻居  贝丝·安·斯坦顿
This is my neighbor, Beth Ann Stanton.
贝丝·安  我侄子恩佐  我给你说的医生
Beth Ann, my nephew, Enzo. The doctor.
幸会  斯坦顿夫人
Nice to meet you, Mrs. Stanton.
我也是
Likewise.
希拉说你是学肿瘤学的
So, Sheila says you studied oncology.
就学了一段时间
For a little while,
-然后我就转去血液学了  -不过
- and then I switched to hematology. - Oh, still,
你肯定还记得很多有用的信息吧
I bet you remember lots of useful tidbits.
也许  有什么需要帮助的
I suppose so. How can I help you?
我在想
Well, I was wondering
你能不能推荐一种癌症
if there was a cancer you could recommend.
-推荐  -比较罕见的
- Recommend? - Something rare.
常人从未听说过的癌症
That no one's ever heard of.
要很严重
It should be serious.
但偶尔也可治愈
Oh, but occasionally curable.
我不太懂...
I'm sorry...
还有病症  她需要了解一些症状
And symptoms. She's gonna need symptoms.
如果能提供一些症状  那就太好了
Oh, some symptoms would be lovely.
等一...
Just wait a...
我们到底在说什么啊
What exactly are we talking about here?
恩佐
Enzo.
我作为你姑妈及一位西西里人跟你讲
I say this to you as your aunt and a Sicilian:
你知道的越少越好
The less you know, the better.
好吧
Okay.
罕见的癌症
Um, rare cancers.
不如...
What about...
上皮样血管内皮细胞瘤
Epithelioid hemangioendothelioma.
再说一遍
Say that again.
不用了吧
I'd rather not.
你得的就是这种癌吗
That's the cancer you have?
它会影响软组织
It affects soft tissue.
我想跟你细说
I'd give you the details,
但是细节太恶心了  我们还要吃芝士火锅呢
but they're disgusting and we're having fondue.
天  你应该让我陪你去看医生的
God, I wish you'd let me go to the doctor's with you.
你总是容易激动
You always get so emotional.
不  还是希拉陪我一起去比较好
No. I prefer to go with Sheila.
我要去摆餐具了
Now, I'm going to set the table.
慢着  起码告诉我你还能活多久
Wait. Wait. At least tell me your prognosis.
我会的  但是我不想败坏晚餐兴致
I will, but I don't want to ruin our meal.
贝丝·安  求你了  告诉我吧
Beth Ann! Please, just tell me!
好吧
Fine.
但我需要你坚强
But I need you to be strong.
你做得到吗  罗伯特
Can you do that for me, Robert?
你能做我的勇敢大男孩吗
Can you be my brave boy?
我可以的
Yeah.
看起来我只剩六个月的时间了
Well, it seems I only have six months to live.
六个月
Six months!
但那不代表我就没有治愈的可能
But that doesn't mean I can't recover.
奇迹每天都在发生
Miracles happen every day.
但是医生说我们应该为最坏情况做打算
But the doctor feels we should prepare for the worst.
听起来他已经不抱希望了
It sounds like he's giving up already.
我们应该换个医生再诊断看看
We should get a second opinion.
不用  就算换个医生又能说什么呢
No. I mean, what is another doctor going to say?
说我没得癌症吗
I don't have cancer?
木已成舟  我们必须接受
No, this is the situation, and we all must accept it.
好吗
Okay?
好吧
Okay.
显然  如果我要对抗癌症
Now, obviously, if I'm going to fight this thing,
我需要你的陪伴
I need you by my side.
寸步不离
Constantly.
我哪儿都不会去
I'm not going anywhere.
你是我妻子
You're my wife.
当我说"至死不渝"时  我是认真的
I meant it when I said, "Till death do us part."
我的心肝宝贝
Oh, my darling.
你可要说话算数
I'm going to hold you to that.
这太难选了
This is hard.
我从没为三个月的旅行打包过行李
I've never packed for a three-month trip before.
打包三个月的行李太容易了
Oh, packing for three months is easy.
我每周末外出都装这么多
I do it every time I go away for the weekend.
这裤子看起来很结实  要不我试下
These look sturdy. Should I try them on?
去试吧
Knock yourself out.
我知道我们说好了你晚我一周飞抵巴黎
Hey, I know we agreed that you'd fly to Paris a week after me,
但是三天难道还不够打掩护吗
but wouldn't three days be enough?
或是两天呢
Or even two?
你连一周都等不了吗
You can't wait one week?
我们要争分夺秒地做爱
We need as much time for sex as possible.
记着  你说过我们要把爱"做"遍欧洲每一座城市
Remember, you said you'd make love to me in every city in Europe.
我一人待一整周要怎么做
What am I supposed to do on my own for a whole week?
用手做[走开]
Beat it.
那可真冷血
That's cold.
我不是说你
Oh, not you.
你觉得如何  喜欢这裤子吗
What do you think? Do you like them?
要这么多口袋何用
Oh, what are all the pockets for?
装东西
Carrying stuff.
徒步攀登阿尔卑斯山时会很有用
They'll be great for hiking over the Alps.
-徒步攀登阿尔卑斯山  -对啊
- Hiking over the Alps? - Yeah.
我的天  我们是去度假还是去逃离纳粹分子呐
Good Lord, are we taking a vacation or fleeing the Nazis?
我才意识到我们想象的旅行好像很不一样
I'm starting to think that we're imagining very different trips.
我们的假期应该是优雅  浪漫的
Well, I want our vacation to be elegant, romantic.
在法兰西剧院看戏的夜晚
Nights at la Comédie-Française,
在马克西姆餐厅享用晚餐
dinner at Maxim's.
可是这些都太贵了  我付不起
Yeah, well, I can't afford those things.
如果你付不起的话...
Oh, well, if that's the problem...
不行  我知道你付得起
No, I know you can afford those things,
但是我不想当你的小白脸
but I-I don't want to feel like your gigolo.
-我有个主意  -什么
- I have an idea. - What?
把我的胸针退回去  把钱拿回来
Return my brooch and get your money back.
这钱能买不少法式蜗牛呢
What you spent on it can buy a whole lot of escargot.
我为你买这胸针是为了向你证明你对我多重要
I bought you this to show you what you mean to me.
那就换种方式证明给我看
Well, find another way to show me.
怎么证明
Like what?
你是个艺术家
You're an artist.
发挥你的想象力
Use your imagination.
拉德福德文身店
好吧
Okay.
我们拭目以待
I'll see what I can come up with.
泰勒
Taylor.
你怎么在这儿
What are you doing here?
我们能谈谈吗
Can we talk for a sec?
我十岁时  我母亲生了重病
My mom got sick when I was ten.
从那时起  只剩我们姊妹相依为命
From that point on, it was just us,
我不得不扛起重任
so I had to step up.
那样也好  因为我学会了掌控局面
But it was good, because I learned to take charge.
我发觉无论面临任何问题
I found out I could figure out the solution
我都可以找到解决办法
to any problem that came my way.
直到昨晚
Until last night.
我在酒店房间一直坐到天明
I sat in that hotel room until dawn
想着要如何化解与伊莱的僵局
trying to figure out how to fix this thing with Eli.
可我想不出办法
And I just can't.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
当伊莱上次嗑药过量时
You know, when Eli O.D.'d last time,
我很清楚要如何做
I knew exactly what to do.
我送他去戒毒所  偿还了他的债务
I got him into rehab, I paid off his debts.
但我觉得他始终有些怨恨我
But I think that a part of him always resented me
恨我用了一种他做不到的方式掌控了大局
for managing the situation in a way that he couldn't.
现在他十分生我的气
And now he's just so angry at me.
我觉得他不会允许我帮他的
And I don't think he'll let me help him.
我很害怕如果我不帮他  以后会出什么事
And I'm so scared of what will happen if I can't.
伊莱又不会死
Eli is not going to die.
他如果继续吸毒  一定会死的
He will if he doesn't stop using.
但好消息是  他依然听你的话
But the good news is he still listens to you.
所以我求求你了
So I am begging you. Please.
你是我最后的希望
You are my last hope.
当然可以了  绝对没问题
Of course, yes. Totally.
我完全是站在你这边的  我保证
I'm totally with you. I promise.
谢天谢地  你不知道这对我意义有多重大
Thank God. You have no idea how much that means to me.
好吧
Okay.
我们必须快速行动
We have to move fast,
要赶在伊莱的剧本稿费到账前
before the money comes in for Eli's script.
你是担心他会把那些钱都用来买毒品吗
You're worried he's gonna spend it all on drugs?
不仅仅是毒品
Not just drugs.
伊莱一旦开始吸毒  出手就阔绰到傻的地步
When Eli's using, he gets stupid generous.
-阔绰到傻的地步  -是啊
- Stupid generous? - Oh, yeah.
上一次  他给每个人都买了礼物
The last time, he bought gifts for everyone.
劳力士手表  设计师名牌鞋
Rolex watches, designer shoes.
他嗑嗨了以后
When he's high,
就希望所有人都跟他一样开心
he just wants everyone to be as happy as he is.
所以  我一直在想办法
So, I've been thinking of ways
能让我们隐秘地进行这个计划
that we can handle this covertly.
我有个主意  但有点疯狂
And I have one idea, but it... it's kind of crazy.
我喜欢疯狂
I like crazy.
伊莱下次洗澡时
The next time Eli's in the shower,
我需要你打开他的手机  查出他所有的密码
I need you to go into his phone and find all of his passwords.
什么
What?
他的手机解锁密码是0429
The code to his phone is 0-4-2-9.
给  我替你写下来了
Just here, look, I wrote it down for you.
如果我们能进入
If we can get access
他的商务账户和信用卡
to his his business accounts and his credit cards,
就能切断他的现金流
we can cut off his cash flow.
并且我还会联系他父亲
And I'm gonna call his dad.
那能有什么帮助
How will that help?
伊莱超级怕他父亲
Eli is terrified of his dad.
杰克会逼他承认是谁让他又复吸了
Jake will force him to admit who got him using again.
那有什么重要的
Why does that matter?
他成功戒毒两年
He was clean for two years,
突然间却又开始吸上了
and then suddenly he's not?
不  我需要知道究竟是怎么回事
No, I need to know what happened.
当然了
Of course.
我也想帮忙  但这真的是最好的计划吗
And I want to help, but is this really the best plan?
你这是什么意思
What do you mean?
你还记得你之前觉得
Look, you remember how you felt when you thought
我和伊莱在合伙对付你  你是什么感觉吧
that Eli and I were ganging up on you.
如果他觉得我们两个合起伙来对付他
How is he gonna feel if it... if it seems like
他又会是什么感觉
we're ganging up on him?
那你建议我们该怎么做
So what do you propose we do?
给我几天时间  我会跟他讲道理  说服他
Give me a few days and I'll reason with him.
你真的觉得你有能力说服他吗
You really think you can talk him into this?
相信我  我会说服他的
Trust me. I'll get through to him,
他会回到家中
he'll come home,
我们又可以成为一家人了
and we'll all be a family again.
瞧瞧这是谁来了
Look who's here!
卡尔  这是希特维尔夫妇
Karl, it's the Sitwells!
你们从苏格兰回来了
You're back from Scotland, I see.
我们还要跟雷克斯和朱莉一起享用晚餐
And we're meeting Rex and Julie for dinner.
他们应该随时都有可能到
They should be here any second.
我爱她  她觉得我很美
Oh, I love her. She thinks I'm pretty.
我们都觉得你很美
We all think you're pretty.
但她会大声说出来
But she says it out loud.
这样吧  等他们到了以后
Tell you what... when they get here,
不如你把他们带去我们那桌吧
why don't you bring them over to our table?
我们一起用餐
We'll dine together.
好极了  那你们就可以跟我们说说
Wonderful. Then you can tell us
你们对于艾米的奢华婚礼的安排了
about your plans for Amy's lavish wedding.
我们太激动了  简直迫不及待
We're so excited. We can't wait.
我也迫不及待
I can't wait, either.
迫不及待让婚礼早点结束
For it to be over.
是啊  我也是同样的想法
Yes, I was thinking the same thing.
我们是很糟糕的人吧
Oof, are we terrible people?
才不是  婚礼是很累人的
No. Weddings are exhausting.
再说了  我们得节省精力
Besides, we need to conserve our energy
用来陪我们的男性情人
for our male lovers.
至少你的情人没有比新郎更年轻
At least yours isn't younger than the groom.
是啊  我觉得新娘的继父
Yeah, I think the, uh, stepfather of the bride
至少该找一个与他年龄相当的男友
should have at least an age-appropriate boyfriend.
就当我老传统吧  但我就是这么想的
Call me old fashioned, but I just do.
卡尔  你脸上这是什么
Oh, Karl. What's that on your face?
什么
What?
天呐  你化了妆吗
Oh, my God, are you wearing makeup?
没你的妆浓
Less than you.
你真是彻底放飞自我了
You really are spreading your wings.
我觉得我出国的时机刚刚好
I think I'm leaving the country in the nick of time.
-我去洗手间了  -我给你叫一杯螺丝锥鸡尾酒
- I'm off to the ladies' room - I'll order you a gimlet.
萨蒙妮
Simone?
嗨
Hi.
你是本奈特医生的妻子  对吧
Uh, you are Dr. Bennett's wife, right?
我叫莫琳  同时我也在他的诊所当护士
Maureen. I also work in his practice as a nurse.
那可真好啊
Well, isn't that nice?
我真的有点难以启齿
I don't know quite how to say this.
但是   你知道你丈夫是同性恋吗
But... do you know your husband's a homosexual?
是的  我知道
Yes, I know.
你这不说得挺直接的嘛
And you said it just fine.
我知道这不关我的事
I realize it's none of my business.
我只是想当个好人
I'm just trying to be a good person.
跟所有好人一样  你就是迫不及待地告诉我这事
And like all good people, you just couldn't wait to tell me.
我要走了  你尽情地补妆吧
I'm going now. Feel free to adjust your halo.
卡尔跟你说了他病了吗
Has Karl told you he's sick?
什么
What?
看来还没有
I can see he hasn't.
卡尔才没病
Karl isn't sick.
他三天前去我丈夫那里就诊了
He saw my husband three days ago.
他也患上了在同性恋男子群体中肆虐的那种疾病
He has that new disease that all the gay men are spreading.
你在说谎
That's a lie.
他是我丈夫见过的第三位患者
He's the third man my husband's seen who's had it.
前两个都已经死了
The first two are dead.
我很遗憾  我只是觉得你应该知道
I'm so sorry. I just thought you should know.
我懂  我懂  我懂
I know, I know, I know,
我知道这听起来难以置信
I know, I know it sounds unbelievable
并且很荒唐  但麻烦稍微忍耐下..
and faintly ridiculous, but bear with me on this...
你好啊  亲爱的  你来的正是时候
Oh, hello, darling. It's perfect timing.
我正在跟大家说我们的威尼斯之旅呢
I was just telling everyone the story of our trip to Venice,
你不小心把那个船夫撞进水里了
when you accidentally knocked that gondolier into the water.
这事是真的吗
Now, did that really happen?
还是卡尔在瞎说
Or is Karl just embellishing?
没有  那种事情卡尔不会撒谎的
No, that-that's not the kind of thing Karl would lie about.
然后他浑身湿漉漉的
So, there he was, dripping wet,
肚子里装满了威尼斯大运河的水
hacking up great lungfuls of the Grand Canal,
我意识到一个人想保持体面
and I realized it's very difficult
是一件很难的事情
to maintain one's dignity...
-嗨  早上你到哪里去了  -出去了
- Hey. Where have you been all morning? - Ah... out.
做事情  准确说是做好事
Doing stuff. Doing great stuff, in fact.
跟我到外面来  我有东西要给你看
Come with me outside. I've got something to show you.
-来吧  -你昨晚都没上床
- Come on. - You never came to bed last night.
你有睡觉吗
Did you get any sleep at all?
没有  我发现不停吸食可卡因
No. No, it turns out one of the side effects
有一点副作用就是  人会有点失眠
of near-constant cocaine use is a wee bit of insomnia.
来吧
Come on.
-哇  -看到了吧
- Oh! Wow! - Right?
你喜欢吗
You like it?
-这个  是你买的吗  -没错
- It... uh... you bought this? - I did.
准确地说是美国运通信用卡买的
Well, uh, technically American Express bought it.
但是我的稿酬一进账
But that bill's gonna get paid
我就会用那笔钱偿付
the second my first script payment comes through.
你喜欢吗
You like it?
听着  我知道你最近非常辛苦
Look, I know you've been working really hard,
我也明白你想奖赏自己
and I get that you'd want to treat yourself...
自己  不是
Me? No. Whoa.
不  不是的  这不是给我买的
No, I didn't... This isn't for me.
你给我买了一辆车
Y-You bought me a car?
是的
I did.
-不会吧  -不骗你
- Shut. Up. - I won't.
这是我对你的感谢
This is me saying thank you.
-为了什么  -天哪  为了一切
- For what? - My God, for everything.
为了你在剧本上给予我的帮助
For all the help you gave me with the script.
为了你在泰勒发疯时  对我的支持
For standing by me when Taylor lost her mind...
天哪  泰勒不会高兴的
Oh, God... Taylor's not gonna like this.
你知道吗  这件事泰勒无权插手  好吗
Well, you know what? Taylor doesn't get a vote, okay?
看起来很贵  你确定吗
It looks expensive. Are you sure?
我给你承诺过  对吗
Well, I made you a promise, right?
我说过等钱进账了
I said when this money came through,
我会照顾你的
I would take care of you.
我生活中有很多人给我许下过承诺
People have made me a lot of promises in my life.
但之前都没人能够遵守
Nobody's ever kept one before.
这是我兑现我的承诺
Well, this is me keeping mine.
而这仅仅是开始
And this is just the beginning.
那么...你喜欢吗
So... do you like it?
太棒了
It's perfect.
一直向前面直走
Just keep going straight.
我做了点功课
So I've been doing some research,
找了些孕妇可以做的工作
finding jobs a pregnant woman can do.
我已经有工作了
I already have a job.
要生产的女人不该做整天站着的工作
You shouldn't be on your feet all day when you're expecting,
不过别担心  对于你这样情况的女孩
but don't worry. There are plenty of ways
还是有很多方法谋生的
a girl in your condition can make a living.
是吗
Are there?
当然了  你可以去保龄球馆做保龄球摆放员
Sure. You could be a pin setter in a bowling alley.
你只需要按按钮就行了
All you'd have to do is punch buttons.
我看到阿纳海姆的一家保龄球馆在招人
I found an opening at an alley in Anaheim.
现在左转
Now take a left.
或者还有个地方在招接线员
Or... there's a place hiring switchboard operators.
不过那份工作你得搬去巴斯托
For that, you'd have to move to Barstow.
听上去你好像想甩掉我似的
It sounds like you're trying to get rid of me.
别傻了
Don't be silly.
我只是觉得在新的城市里
I just thought it might be easier for you
你能够更容易有个好的开始
to make a fresh start in a new city.
-我不会搬走的  -好吧
- Well, I'm not moving. - Okay.
记住我会在你身边
Just know I'm here for you.
为你提供一切所需
For anything you need.
谢谢
Thank you.
停车吧  到了
Oh... uh, pull over, this is it.
你弄错了吧
This must be a mistake.
医生才不会把诊所开在这种地方
A doctor wouldn't have his office in here.
不  就是这里
No, this is it.
你确定你把地址记对了吗
Are you sure you have the address right?
希拉  我骗了你  我不是来见医生的
Sheila, I lied. I'm not here to see a doctor.
我不明白
I don't understand.
抱歉  我不能要这个孩子
I'm sorry. I just can't have this baby.
你到底在说什么
What are you talking about?
请别让我大声说出来
Please do not make me say this out loud.
你要干的这件事  是不合法的
What you're going to do, it's illegal.
我知道
I know.
天哪  你到底是从哪里听来的这个地方
God, how did you even hear about this place?
餐馆的一个女孩推荐我来的
A girl at the diner referred me.
你
You...
抱歉
Excuse me.
你不能这么做  这是不对的
You can't do this, it's not right.
希拉  请别再给我增添负担了
Sheila, please do not make this harder than it already is.
我是萨利·琼斯  我们通过电话
I'm Sally Jones. We spoke on the phone.
她是谁
Who's she?
我的朋友
My friend.
做完她要载我回家
She'll drive me home afterwards.
-带钱了吗  -带了
- You got the money? - I do.
进来吧
Come on in.
希拉  拜托
Sheila. Please.
我现在比任何时候都需要朋友
I really need a friend right now, more than ever.
-给你  孩子  -谢谢你  先生
- Here you go, son. - Thank you, sir.
我马上为您把车开过来
I'll have your car here in just a second.
-美好的一晚  -见到你们太开心了
- Terrific night. - Lovely seeing you all.
我们隔几天再聚一次吧
Let's do it again very soon.
晚安  萨蒙妮  婚礼再见吧
Good night, Simone. See you at the wedding.
好了  现在没人了  你可以说了
All right, we're alone. You can tell me now.
说什么
Tell you what?
我又怎么惹你了  别说你没事
How I've upset you. And don't say you're fine.
整晚上你就没跟我说几句话
You've barely said two words to me the entire evening.
等到车里再说
Wait till we're in the car.
能不能给点提示
Can I at least have a headline?
我在洗手间撞上你医生的妻子了
I ran into your doctor's wife in the ladies' room.
我不记得有见过她
Don't think I've ever met her.
她也是名护士
She also works as a nurse.
在他诊所里
In his office.
她说了什么
What did she say?
你生病了
You're sick.
我说两件事  第一
Well, two things: first of all...
我没病
I'm not sick.
第二  她真是个八婆
Secondly, what a gossipy bitch.
-你是说她撒谎了吗  -我没有症状
- Are you saying she lied? - I'm not... symptomatic.
-我觉得没事  -那你化妆是在掩藏什么
- I feel fine. - So what's the makeup hiding?
一个脓疱
A spot.
-你是说病变吗  -拜托
- Don't you mean a lesion? - Oh, come on,
那很小
it's miniscule.
你知道我有多害怕吗
Do you have any idea how scared I am?
-你没有感染  -什么
- You don't have it. - What?
事实是  这病只能通过血液
Look, the fact is, it can only be transmitted through blood
或者体液传播  我们很少有性生活
or bodily fluids, and we rarely had sex,
就算有也都是戴了套的
and never without a condom.
你是这么想的吗
Is that what you think?
-我是在为自己担心  -亲爱的
- That I'm scared for myself? - Darling, darling, darling,
我  我应该告诉你的
I, I, I... I should have told you,
亲爱的  我只是...
my love, I just...
我  我不想破坏了你的旅行
I did... I just didn't want to spoil your trip.
天  旅行
Oh, God, the trip.
我很抱歉  我保证
Look, I'm so sorry. I-I-I-I promise
你走期间我会每周给你打一次电话
I... I-I will call once a week while you're away,
告诉你病情的最新进展
with, with full medical updates.
你觉得我还会去吗
You think I'm still going?
在这种时候离开你
That I'd leave you at a time like this?
你留下来又能改变什么呢
And what would staying achieve?
除了让我知道
Other than letting me know
你觉得我挺不过劳工节
that you think I won't make it past Labor Day?
你需要关照  卡尔
You need care, Karl.
专家  而且得找个妻子
Specialists. And at least one doctor whose wife
不是大嘴巴的医生
is not the goddamn town crier!
我知道汤米对你有多重要
I know how much Tommy means to you.
我要留下来陪你  没有
I'm staying with you, and that is the end
商量的余地
of this discussion.
谢谢你
Thank you.
-你想喝点威士忌吗  -威士忌
- Do you want some whiskey? - Whiskey?
在你开始前喝醉对你有好处
It's good to get a little drunk before you start.
能缓解疼痛
Helps with the pain.
-不了  谢谢  -随你便
- No, thank you. - Suit yourself.
给我几分钟
Just give me a couple of minutes.
我得在桌上铺点塑料
I got to get some plastic over the table.
她要在厨房里做吗
She's doing this in the kitchen?
显然是的
Apparently.
可这是侵入性操作
But it's an invasive procedure.
需要干净的环境  消毒器械
It requires a clean environment. Sterilized instruments.
我只能负担起这个了
Well, this is all I can afford.
我无计可施了  希拉
I'm out of options, Sheila.
请理解
Please understand.
有件事你不知道
There's something you don't know.
我得告诉你
There's something I need to tell you.
什么事
What's that?
我曾有个孩子
I had a child once,
但她过世了
but she died.
我没有关上后院的大门
I left the gate to the backyard open.
她漫步到了街上
She wandered out into the street
被车撞了
and she was hit by a car.
已经过去了很多年  但我每天都在想她
It's been years, but I think about her every day.
有时在深夜
Sometimes, late at night,
我会想要是她还活着  她会长成一个怎样的女人
I wonder what kind of young woman she'd have turned into.
你怎么能在此时此刻跟我说这种事
How could you tell me something like that right now?
你想要我感到内疚吗
Are you... are you trying to make me feel guilty?
不  你不明白
No, you don't understand.
不  不明白的是你  希拉
No, I think you don't understand, Sheila.
-我必须这么做  -亲爱的  我想说的是
- I have to do this. - Honey, I'm trying to say...
我想我女儿长大后会很像你
I think my daughter would have grown up to be a lot like you.
这也是我爱你的原因之一
That is one of the reasons I love you.
但现在我为你担心
But right now I'm afraid for you
因为女人会在这样的地方死去
because women die in places like this.
我不能允许这样的事发生
I can't let that happen.
希拉  我单身还没钱
Sheila, I'm single and I'm broke.
我没能力抚养小孩
I can't raise a baby.
我们会想出办法的  我们只是需要时间思考
We'll figure it out. We just need time to think.
-让我帮你  -怎么帮
- Let me help you. - How?
我
Well, I'll...
我会  我会去筹一些钱
I'll get some... I'll get my hands on some money.
我们可以去别的地方  一个安全的地方  但是拜托
We can go somewhere else, somewhere safe, but please,
离开这里
let's get out of here.
好的
Okay. Okay.
喂
Hello?
我就是
Yeah, this is she.
没  我的美国运通信用卡没丢  怎么了
No, I haven't lost my Amex. Why?
可疑活动
Suspicious activity?
花了多少钱
Um, how much was spent?
车子不错
Nice car.
泰勒
Taylor.
-你刚从家里出来吗  -我是来找伊莱的
- Were you in the house? - I came to talk to Eli
好让他给我解释为什么我的信用卡被刷爆了
so he could explain to me why my credit card is maxed out,
然后我看到你停下这辆崭新的车
and then I saw you pull up in this brand-new car.
我不知道他什么时候回家
Well, I-I don't know when he'll be home.
他要在派拉蒙参加一个会议
He has a meeting at Paramount and...
这是他买给你的  对吗
He bought it for you, didn't he?
我跟他说了这太贵重
I told him it was too much.
-什么时候  -他给我的那一刻
- When? - The moment he gave it to me.
不  我是问他什么时候给你的
No. I'm asking when did he give it to you?
在我今早在公园里看到你之前还是之后
Before I saw you in the park this morning or after?
之后
After.
那你怎么没坚持退回去
So why didn't you insist he take it back?
我很意外  我不知道该说什么
I was so surprised, I didn't know what to say.
意外  洁德  我刚跟你说了伊莱嗨了以后
Surprised? Jade, I had just told you that when Eli is high,
-他就会乱花钱  -我不认为这是乱花钱
- he's stupid with money. - Well, I don't think it's stupid.
我每天要做饭  打扫
I spend every day cooking and cleaning,
跑腿  照顾你俩
running errands and looking after you both.
我觉得这很好  终于有人
I think it's nice that someone actually
想说谢谢了
wanted to say thank you.
你想有人谢谢你  行  洁德
You want a thank you? Okay, fine, Jade.
谢谢
Thank you.
钥匙给我
Now give me the keys.
-为什么  -因为我要把车退回去
- Why? - 'Cause I'm gonna return the car, obviously.
不
No.
-你这是什么啥意思  -你不能把车退掉
- What do you mean no? - You can't return the car.
车不是你的  是伊莱买给我的
It's not yours. Eli bought it for me.
但他是因为嗑药嗑疯了才买的
Yeah, but he's coked out of his mind.
接受一个这种情况下男人送的礼物
To accept a gift from a man in that condition
"吃相"可不太好看
is not a good look.
天  你为什么这样子
My God. Why are you acting like this?
我没有做过任何错事
I haven't done anything wrong.
你是在趁人之危
You are taking advantage of this situation.
你在利用伊莱  钥匙给我
You're using Eli. Just give me the keys.
够了  要说谁是使用者[瘾君子]的话
Stop it. If anyone is a user,
那也是你  泰勒  你利用了我好几个月了
Taylor, it's you. You have been using me for months.
我救了你  我让你住进我家
I saved you. I brought you into my home.
你那是为了你自己  不是我
You did that for yourself, not for me.
你的婚姻分崩离析  你需要一个分心的事物
Your marriage was falling apart and you needed a distraction.
伊莱写不出剧本  赚不到钱
Eli wasn't writing or making money,
你很生气
and you were so angry
你几乎都不正眼看他
you could barely even look at him.
对了  是我让他再次开始写作的
By the way, I'm the one who got him writing again.
我是为了你
I did that for you.
不用谢
You're welcome.
我一直在想为什么伊莱复吸
I keep wondering why Eli started using again.
是因为你IMA
Are you the reason?
天呐  我们不该这样
Oh, my God. We shouldn't be doing this.
吵架  互相责备
Fighting and throwing blame at each other.
我们应该是一家人的
We're supposed to be a family.
够了  够了  洁德
Stop it. Stop it, Jade!
我和伊莱是一家人
Eli and I are a family.
你是房客
You are a houseguest.
仅此而已
That's all.
知道吗  洁德  上楼
You know what, Jade? Go upstairs,
收拾你的东西  我要你立刻离开我家
get your stuff. I want you out of my house now!
想得美
That's not gonna happen.
你要想的话你可以再次离开
You can leave again if you want,
我反正是不会走的
but I'm not going anywhere,
而且我要把车留下
and I'm keeping the car.
我不会让你把它夺走
I'm not gonna let you take it away from me.
汤米  进来
Tommy, come in.
嗨  我有好消息
Hi. I have great news.
我把你的胸针退掉了  我给你买了替代礼品
I returned your brooch and I got your replacement gift.
不是传统意义上的礼物
Well, it's not a traditional gift
只是对你表达敬意
so much as a tribute to you.
我希望你喜欢  因为
I sure hope you like it because, uh,
我不能退掉
I can't really return it.
你看着不开心  怎么了
Hey. You look sad. What's wrong?
我们得谈谈
We need to talk.
好消息
Hey. Hey, great news.
派拉蒙想让我改编一本小说
Paramount wants to talk to me about adapting a novel.
我周五要去开会  我跟你说
I got a meeting on Friday. I'm telling you,
我是真的要东山再起了
this comeback shit is really starting to get real.
我真的为你感到开心
I'm really, really happy for you.
怎么了
What's wrong?
泰勒之前来了
Taylor stopped by.
我猜你们的见面不是很和谐  对吗
I'm guessing that didn't go so well, huh?
伊莱
Oh, Eli.
我讨厌这样
I hate this.
我讨厌她让我陷入这种境地
I hate that she's putting me in this position.
什么境地  你在说什么
What position? What are you talking about?
她想让我搞到你账户的密码
She wants me to get the passwords to your accounts,
这样她就能拿走你所有的钱
so she can take away all your money.
取消旅行
Cancel the trip?
我不能在卡尔生病时离开
I can't leave when Karl is sick.
可他都没有住院
Yeah, but-but he's not even in the hospital.
暂时还没  但这个病无法预测
Not yet, but this disease is unpredictable.
我得留下来
I need to be here.
不  这不公平  这本应是
No, that's not fair. This was supposed to be
我这辈子最棒的一个夏天
the best summer of my life.
这也可能是卡尔一生里最后一个夏天
And this could be the last summer of Karl's life,
所以拜托别生气了
so please stop sulking.
-你在干什么  -我要喝酒
- What are you doing? - I need a drink.
你才刚满18岁
You're barely 18.
嗯  跟你交往让我成熟了很多
Yeah, well, dating you has aged me.
给我
Give me that.
一周  这是我唯一要求
One week, that's all I ask.
一周时间不会发生任何事的
Nothing can happen in-in a-a week.
那有什么意义  我不会开心的
What would be the point? I wouldn't enjoy myself.
跟我一起去巴黎都不开心吗
In Paris? With me?
我丈夫要死了
My husband is dying.
你不明白这意味着什么吗
Can you not understand what that means?
那我们的关系会怎样
So what's gonna happen to us?
我想"我们"是成不了的
I don't think there can be an "Us."
听着
Look...
我知道有时我的行为像小孩
I know that I can act like a kid sometimes,
但如果你再给我次机会  我可以更加成熟
but if you give me another chance, I can be more mature.
不
No.
你保持年轻就好
You stay young.
需要成长的人是我
I'm the one who needs to grow up.
可能是卡尔的医生打来的
That might be Karl's doctor.
我要去隔壁房间接
I, I'm gonna take it in the other room.
-萨蒙妮  -不
- Simone... - No.
汤米
Tommy.
好极了
All right, great,
你今天就能把钱转走  对吗
and you can transfer those funds today, right?
好的  谢谢  回头聊  再见
All right, thank you. Yeah, I'll talk to you. Bye.
好了  我的业务经理在处理了
All right. All right, so my business manager's on it.
他会重置我所有账户的密码
He's gonna reset the passwords to all my accounts.
我跟拉马尔谈了  我禁止他和泰勒交流
And I spoke to Lamar. I forbid him to speak to Taylor,
这样她就不能利用他来获得我的剧本报酬
so she can't use him to try to get to my script payments.
真是松了口气
That's a relief.
你觉得这样做够了吗
Do you think it'll be enough?
什么意思
What do you mean?
我们之前出去的时候  泰勒来过
Taylor was here, in the house, while we were out.
或许我们该换锁
Maybe we should think about changing the locks.
她是我老婆  她爱我
Whoa. Uh, I mean, she's my wife and she loves me.
她只是想用她的方式保护我
In her way she's just trying to protect me.
她是想控制你
She's trying to control you.
两者是有区别的
There's a difference.
我不知道
I don't know.
也许我该给她打电话
I mean, maybe I should just call her.
不
No!
我知道你想相信她会回心转意
I mean, I know you want to believe that she's gonna come around,
但你得明白  她永远不可能
but you have to know, deep down, there's no way she's ever
同意你吸毒
gonna get on board with the idea of you using.
她还威胁要告诉你爸
And she's threatening to call your dad.
我爸  你逗我吗
My dad? Are you fucking kidding me?
为什么
Why?
她知道我不跟他说话的  该死
She knows that I don't speak to him. Goddamn it.
她不能这么做
She can't just fucking do that.
她想让你觉得渺小
She's trying to make you feel small.
我讨厌她这么对你
I hate that she's treating you this way.
我最不想看到的就是你失去
The last thing I want is to see you lose everything
你为之努力赚取的一切
you've been working so hard to get.
你给谁打电话
Who are you calling?
我们的勤杂工  你说得对
Our handyman. You're right.
我们得把锁换了
We're gonna change those fucking locks.
罗伯有很多运动装备
Rob's got an awful lot of old sports equipment.
他从来不用
And he never uses any of it.
我要把它们拿去当了
So I'm taking it to the pawnshop
然后把钱给艾普尔
and giving the cash to April.
那可有不少钱啊
Well, that'll be a nice chunk of change.
要是她不用过多担心钱的话
It will be easier for her to make a rational decision about the baby
在孩子问题上她会更容易做出理智的决定
if she's not so worried about money.
我还是无法相信你竟然说服了她不去堕胎
I still can't believe you talked her out of it.
那个可怕的地方  我实在看不下去
That horrible place? I couldn't let her stay.
拿着  放到箱子里
Here, put this in the big pile, please.
我得承认我有点没想到
I got to admit I'm a bit surprised.
没想到
Surprised?
她怀上了你老公的孩子
She's pregnant with your husband's kid.
大多数妻子在这种情况下
Most wives in that situation
根本不会在乎刀有多钝
wouldn't care how rusty the knives were.
不能让艾普尔或者她孩子出事
Couldn't let anything happen to April or her baby.
亲爱的  你知道她还是可以决定打掉的吧
Honey, y-you know that she could still decide to get rid of it.
我知道  所以接下来几天里
I know. That's why I have to work hard
我要更加努力改变她的主意
over the next few days to change her mind.
跟她说说领养
Well, talk to her about adoption.
有很多好人
You know, there's-there's plenty of nice people out there
不孕不育
who can't have kids.
我会跟她说的
I'll mention that.
还有一个可能
There's also another possibility.
是什么
What's that?
我和罗伯可以抚养那孩子
Rob and I could raise the baby.
什么
What?
我都想好了
I've got it all figured out.
我会一直陪着艾普尔直到孩子出世
I'll support April until the baby arrives,
然后我会提出抚养它
then I'll offer to raise it.
就罗伯而言  我可以计划一个方案
As far as Rob's concerned, I could arrange some scenario,
比如在公园里的摇篮车里发现被抛弃的孩子
finding it in a bassinet in a park, abandoned.
没人需要知道真相
No one would ever have to know the truth.
罗伯可以拥有自己的孩子  艾普尔也能有自己的事业
Rob would have his child, April could have her career,
皆大欢喜
everyone would be happy.
怎么了
What's wrong?
一开始我还觉得挺好玩的
At first I thought it was funny,
你和你老公的母狗成了朋友
you becoming friends with your husband's slut.
-希拉  别用那词  -然后  当你和她
- Sheila, that word. - And then, when you kept getting
走得越来越近  我以为你有点疯癫
closer to her, I thought you were a little nutty.
但是不是  你是变态
But no. You're sick.
我不是变态
I'm not sick.
你孩子死了
Your kid is dead.
你想用艾普尔的孩子替代她
And you're trying to replace her with April's baby.
才不是这样
That is not what I'm doing.
从我的角度看  你就是在这么做
That is what you're doing from where I'm standing.
你没资格评判我
You're not allowed to judge me.
除非你给本尼挑选了棺材
Not until you pick out Benny's casket
为他穿上最美的衣服
and dress him in his Sunday best
将他葬于地下
and put him in the ground.
在那之前  我不想再听到你的
Until you do that, I don't want to hear another word
任何一句话
from you.
喂
Hello?
萨蒙妮  还好你接了
Simone, thank God you answered.
娜奥米  怎么了
Naomi. What's going on?
我没带钱包就出门了
I ran out without my purse,
我没有医保卡和身份证
and I don't have my insurance card or my ID,
女管家也没接电话
and the housekeeper isn't answering,
我不知道还能打给谁
and I don't have anyone else to call.
慢点  出什么事了  你在哪
Slow down. What's going on? Where are you?
我在医院
I'm at the hospital.
我需要我的钱包  你能带过来吗
I need my purse. Can you please bring it?
当然  怎么了
Well, of course. What's happened?
汤米出车祸了
Tommy's been in a car accident.
我马上过来
I-I'll be right there.
你好  有何贵干
Yes. Can I help you?
我是来找罗伯·斯坦顿的
I'm here to speak to Rob Stanton.
-你有预约吗  -没
- Do you have an appointment? - No.
不跟他说上话我就不走
But I'm not leaving until I speak to him.
你说什么
I beg your pardon?
跟他说是艾普尔找她
Tell him it's April.
所以你知道我是谁
So you know who I am.
是的
I do.
抱歉  但他不会见你
I'm sorry, but he won't see you.
你真的该走了
I really think that you should go.
小姐
Miss!
请停下
Please stop.
抱歉  斯坦顿先生
I'm sorry, Mr. Stanton.
我跟她说了你很忙
I told her you were busy.
没事  你想要什么
It's all right. What do you want?
占用你一分钟
One lousy minute of your time.
这是你欠我的  你不觉得吗
You owe me that, don't you think?
克莱尔  出去  把门关上
Claire, go ahead and shut the door.
抱歉我没有回你电话
I'm sorry I didn't return your phone calls.
我想着一刀两对更好
I thought a clean break was just better for...
我怀孕了
I'm pregnant.
别担心  我不需要你给我什么
Don't worry. I don't need anything from you.
我不会留着
I'm not keeping it.
你对待我的方式
The way you treated me,
我本来不想告诉你的
I wasn't even going to tell you.
但我不是坏人
But I'm not a bad person.
你有权知道
You have a right to know.
总之  这就是我来此想对你说的
Anyway, that's all I came here to say, so...
再见
goodbye.
祝你生活美满
Have a nice life.
等等
Wait.
萨蒙妮  太谢谢你了
Simone, thank you so much.
-汤米在哪  -他们在扫描他的头部
- Where's Tommy? - They're doing some scans of his head.
他可能有脑震荡
He has a possible concussion.
他们要确保没有任何肿胀
They need to be sure there's no swelling.
但他不会有事
But he'll be all right?
他受了很多伤
He's pretty banged up.
他腿上划了道口子  不过他会好起来的
He has a bad cut on his leg, but he'll recover.
-谢天谢地  -他醉酒驾驶
- Oh, thank God. - He was driving while drunk.
护士告诉我的时候我完全不敢相信
I couldn't believe it when the nurse told me.
汤米绝不会...
Tommy would never...
天  我的儿子到底怎么了
God. What's happened to my boy?
我感觉好惭愧
I feel so awful.
你能来真好
You're so sweet to be here.
尤其是现在你还要应付自己的难事
Even now, when you're going through your own hell.
什么意思
What do you mean?
我知道卡尔的事了
I know about Karl,
他染上了那个同志疾病
how he's sick with that gay disease.
我不知道你听说了什么  但是
I don't know what you've heard, but...
艾达·考伊跟我说了
Ida Coy told me.
她在厕所隔间里
She was in one of the stalls
听到了你和本奈特医生的妻子之间的对话
when you were talking to Dr. Bennett's wife.
天呐  求你别再告诉任何人了
Oh, God. Well, please don't tell anyone else.
卡尔一定会很生气的
Karl would be so upset.
我才不在乎卡尔
I don't care about Karl.
我担心的是你
You're the one I'm concerned for.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
如果你是想问我有没有被染病  我没有
Well, I don't have it, if that's what you're asking.
但愿没有吧
Well, I hope not.
现在我似乎明白那些人是怎么让这病肆虐的了
No one seems to know how those people are spreading it.
我们把你儿子带去了房间里  想见可以去见了
We brought your son to a room if you want to see him.
好的  拜托了  我们走
Yes, please, let's go.
但后面只允许家属进去
Oh, but we can only allow family back there.
萨蒙妮也几乎算是家人了
Oh, Simone is practically family.
抱歉  这是规定
Sorry, it's policy.
-没事  你回头打电话给我吧  -我会的
- It's fine. Just-just call me later. - I will.
如果你需要我  我一定会支持你的
And I will be there for you when you need me.
事实是  我爱上洁德的时候
Truth is, I fell in love with Jade
完全不清楚她是个什么样的人
without really knowing who she was.
更糟糕的是  我把她带进了我的家中
And what's worse is I brought her into my home.
现在她睡在我的床上  我却住在酒店里
Now she's sleeping in my bed and I'm living in a hotel.
我要她滚出我家
I need her out of my house.
但我那吸毒的丈夫现在完全听她的
But she's enabling my drug addict husband
限制区域
我觉得他是不会放她离开的
and I don't think he'll just let her go.
更别提你我都清楚
Not to mention the fact that you and I both know
当她觉得受到威胁时  会做出多么过激的反应
how intensely she can react when she feels threatened.
如果我要把她赶出我家  我需要聪明点
If I'm gonna get her out of the house, I need to be smart.
我需要筹码
I need leverage.
我觉得你可能是帮助我的最佳人选
And I thought you might be just the person to help me with that.
我为什么要帮你
Why would I help you?
我的想法是  你帮我挠背  我也帮你挠背
I'm thinking, you scratch my back, I scratch yours.
你只需要告诉我哪里痒就行了
All you got to do is tell me where it itches.
他们把我的保释金定成了1万美元
They set my bail at $10,000.
他们似乎觉得我很危险
They seem to think I'm dangerous.
算你走运  我带支票簿来了
Well, as luck would have it, I brought my checkbook.
那样的话  我能帮上你什么忙
Well, in that case, how can I help?
把你知道的关于洁德的一切都告诉我
Tell me everything you know about Jade.
首先  那不是她的真名
Well, for starters, that's not her real name.
妈的
Oh, shit.
等等  亲爱的  更劲爆的还在后面呢
Hold on, darling. You ain't heard nothing yet.
我可怜的宝贝
Oh, my poor baby.
他的腿怎么样了
How is his leg?
不得不缝了几针
Well, he needed some stitches,
不过很快就能恢复如初了
but he will be good as new in no time.
这是什么鬼
What in the world?
萨蒙妮
萨蒙妮是谁
Who's Simone?
是他女朋友吗
That his girlfriend?
这么年轻就文身
Bit young for a tattoo.
以后情变了肯定会后悔的
One day he's gonna regret that.
她也会后悔的
So will she.
你好啊
Hey there.
感觉怎么样
How you feeling?
你来了  我就觉得好多了
Better, now that you're here.
需要我帮忙做点什么吗
Need help with anything?
我只是在给土豆削皮而已  我觉得我可以应付
Oh, I'm just peeling potatoes. I think I can handle it.
我去换身衣服
I'm gonna change clothes.
等我换完  我要下来帮你摆桌子
When I'm done, I'll come down and set the table for you.
你太贴心了
You're sweet.
利奥
Leo.
你怎么来了
What are you doing here?
罗伯去哪儿了
Where's Rob?
他刚刚上楼了  是出什么事了吗
He just went upstairs. Is something wrong?
是的  你需要去我家一趟
Yeah, you need to come to our house.
那个人给你打来电话了
You got a phone call from you-know-who.
她说有要紧的事
She said it's important.
希拉希望我告诉你
And Sheila wanted me to tell you
这是她最后一次帮你了
this is the last time she's doing this for you.
她还在生我的气吗
She's still angry with me?
是啊  差不多吧
Yeah, something like that.
你觉得我是个糟糕的人吗
Do you think I'm a horrible person?
不  我认为你是个好女人
Nah, I think you're a nice lady
只是陷入了大麻烦中
who's gotten herself in a real fucking mess.
我们来了
We're here.
她是认真的吗
Is she serious?
是的
Oh, yeah.
喂
Hello?
希拉  你怎么这么久才来
Sheila. What took you so long?
说来话长  一切都还好吧
Long story. I-Is everything okay?
简直好极了  好到不能再好
Better than okay. Everything is wonderful.
跟我说说
Tell me.
我去了罗伯的办公室  告诉他我怀孕的事
I went to Rob's office to let him know that I'm pregnant.
你干了什么
You did what?
我觉得那个混蛋有权知道
I figured the S.O.B. had a right to know.
总之  我冲进他的办公室  把这事抖出来了
Anyway, I stormed into his office and I blurted it out,
你知道那个笨蛋干了什么吗
and do you know what that big galoot did?
不知道
No.
他单膝跪地
He got down on one knee
问我愿不愿意嫁给他
and asked me if I would marry him.
但是  他还没离婚啊
But no, but he's still married.
我也是这么说的
That's what I said.
但他说他的婚姻就快结束了
But he told me that his marriage is ending.
他说只要再给他六个月的时间就行了
He said he just needs six months.
六个月
Six months.
到时候
And then
他就会彻底自由了
he'll be totally free.
总之  我只想打个电话先告诉你
Anyway, I just wanted to call to tell you first.
接下来我要打电话告诉我妈了
Now I have to call and tell my mother.
希拉
Oh, Sheila.
我真是太幸福了
I am so happy.
我倒是想问问你是不是遇到什么事了
I would ask if everything's okay, but, uh,
但好像我不能再跟你说话了
I don't think I'm allowed to talk to you anymore.
所以...
So...
泰勒:
打给我  我们要谈谈洁德的事
泰勒
屏蔽该号码
屏蔽联系人
取消